# Peter Karki

# Creative Developer

## SUMMARY

I'm a creative developer with 3 years of experience in graphic design and 2 years in game development. My foundation in Computer Science gives me a solid grasp of both programming and graphic designing, enabling the creation of visually appealing and systematic software solutions.

Strengths: Interpersonal Skills, Results Oriented, Life-long Learner

## EXPERIENCE

Full Time Game Developer, Paracosma Nepal Paracosma: Mixed Reality Solution Provider (2022 - Present)

- Developed AR and VR training simulation games for the medical and industrial sector.
- Used motion capture and virtual production in Unreal Engine to create engaging game trailers.
- Assisted the team with graphical and 3D requirements as needed

### 3D Web Developer, Paracosma Nepal

- Developed 3D library site for gas and vehicle company.
- Create landing page for 3D model player marketing page.

# Part Time Graphic designer, Tuddrom Nepal Tuddrom: Earphone Reseller, Nepal (2021)

 Designed graphical banners, social media posts, and managed social media handles.

# Part Time Graphic designer, G-force Security G-Force: Security Service Provider (2019 – 2020)

 Designed product resell graphics, fesEval-themed designs, informaEonal moEon graphics, and office document layouts.

# • EDUCATION

Sunway international college – Maiti Devi Marg, Kathmandu – BCS (HONS) (Infrastructure University Kuala Lumpur)

Graduate

Duration: 2019-2022

CGPA: 3.703

Herald international college – Basundhara, Kathmandu– Science (Physic)/ Highschool

Graduate

Duration: 2016-2018

CGPA: 2.65



## TECHNICAL SKILL

#### **Game Development:**

Unreal (Virtual ProducEon)
Unity (Game Developer / XR)
(VR/AR Developer) / (VP Artist)



#### Web Development Skill:

MERN Stack



#### **Programming Proficiency:**

JavaScript, C/C++, Python and c#



#### **Design Tools:**

Photoshop, Affinity Designer, Adobe Premium Pro, Figma, Adobe After Effect, DaVinci Resolve and Blender





+977 9843809687





